不要在说什么杰斐逊杀人没杀人
Change the conversation from whether or not Jefferson's a murderer
也不要在说是什么管教公司的失职才致使了整个暴乱的开始
to whether or not MCC's negligence incited the riot to begin with.
等等  请问典狱长大人是在叫我搞臭她的监狱吗
Wait. Is the warden really telling me to shit on her prison?
我只是临时的
Interim warden.
而且我跟你先说好  我可不是那种会为了你的幸福
And just so we're clear, I'm not that kind of girlfriend
牺牲掉自己的那种女朋友
who's gonna sacrifice her career for your happiness.
我说着这一切都是为了跟琳达作对
I am just saying all this to fuck with Linda.
你是我女朋友
You are my girlfriend.
- 你绝对是我女朋友  - 闭嘴  闭嘴啦
- You are so my girlfriend. - Shut up. Shut up.
- 别闹  别闹呀  - 你绝对是我女朋友没跑了
- Shut up. Shut up. - You are so my girlfriend!